Reformatting Notes:
- remove <NEWREFERENCE> and subsequent characters
- enclose within <bibl></bibl>
- change title to <title level="a"> </title>
- change journal to <title level="j"> </title>
- change volume to <biblScope unit="volume"> </biblScope>
- change page to <biblScope unit="page"> <biblScope>
- change booktitle to <title level="m"> </title>
    - NOTE: some booktitles missing end tag </booktitle>
- change address to <pubPlace> </pubPlace>
- remove brackets from date and place outside of <date> (fahl file only)
- change year <year> to <date> (kibl and utgo files only)


Annotation guidelines below on how to format citations for GROBID citation_model
taken from: https://grobid.readthedocs.io/en/latest/training/Bibliographical-references/

<author> for the complete sequence of authors

<orgname type="collaboration"> a collaboration is a project-based grouping of authors from different affiliations limited in time. Some examples: In high energy particules the ATLAS, CMS and DELPHI collaborations (the current world record holder for number of authorship arXiv:1503.07589 combines the two CERN collaborations ATLAS and CMS), or the LUNA collaboration in astrophysics. The particularity of collaborations is to be used both as authorship and affiliation component.

<title level="a"> for article title and chapter title. Here "a" stands for analytics (a part of a monograph)

<title level="j"> for journal title

<title level="s"> for series title (e.g. "Lecture Notes in Computer Science")

<title level="m"> for non journal bibliographical item holding the cited article, e.g. conference proceedings title. Note if a book is cited, the title of the book is annotated with <title level="m">. If a thesis is cited, the title of the thesis is annotated with <title level="m">, and the type of thesis as <note type="report">. Here m stands for monograph.

<date> the date sequence (excluding parenthesis, etc.)

<biblScope unit="page"> the full range of pages of the article

<biblScope unit="volume"> the value of the volume (e.g. vol. <biblScope unit="volume">7</biblScope>,)

<biblScope unit="issue"> the value of the issue, also known as number, (e.g. no. <biblScope type="issue">3</biblScope>,)

<orgName> the institution for theses or technical reports

<publisher> the name of the publisher

<pubPlace> publication place, or location of the "publishing" institution

<editor> for all the sequence of editors

<ptr type="web"> for web URL

<idno> for the document-specific identifier, in particular DOI and arXiv identifiers, optionally the type of identifier can be given by the attribute @type, for instance, <idno type="doi">...</idno>, for report identifiers <idno type="report">...</idno> is used

<note type="report"> in the case of technical report at large, encode the indication of the kind of report, this includes "technical report" from an institution, but also the kind of thesis ("Ph.D. thesis", "M.Sc. thesis", etc.)

<note> for any indications related to the reference and not covered by one of the previous tags (for instance "personal communication")
